findmelove.com 2016-04-05

# Find Me Love | www.findmelove.com

September 28, 2014

JDI Dating Ltd (the “Company”, “us”, “we” or “our”) are committed to protecting and respecting your privacy.

This document ,together with our Terms and Conditions of Use (the “Terms”) and any other documents referred to in it, sets out the basis on which any personal data we collect from you, or that you provide to the Company, will be processed by us (our “Privacy Policy). Please read the following carefully to understand our views and practices regarding your personal data and how we will treat it. 

We are the data controller of findmelove.com (the “Website”) for the purposes of the Data Protection Act 1998 (the “Act”). We can be contacted via support@date-support.com or our registered office at Station House, North Street, Havant, Hampshire, United Kingdom, PO91QU 

We may from time to time review and amend this Privacy Policy to take into account changes in law, technology and/or our operations. We will post any changes to this Privacy Policy on the Website from time to time and, when appropriate, notify you by email. Please periodically review this Privacy Policy before using the Website as continued use of the Website shall indicate your acceptance of any changes. All personal information held by us will be governed by the most recent Privacy Policy posted on the Website. We indicate at the top of the page when this Privacy Policy was last updated. 

**What information do we collect about you?**

We may collect and process the following information about you:

  * Information that you provide by filling in forms on the Website (including your personal details, contact details and other Registration Data that you submit when you create an Account). We may also collect information when you voluntarily complete additional profile information, forms, customer surveys, provide feedback and participate in competitions. 

  * If you contact us, we may keep a record of that correspondence. 

  * Details of transactions you carry out through the Website, including any information we require to provide the Services that you order from us through the Website, including Subscription, Product and Credit Fees. 

  * Personal information if you post or transmit information via the Website to other Members and/or Subscribers. 

  * Website usage information is also collected using cookies (see below under 'Cookies'), including but not limited to, traffic data and location data. 

  * Information from other sources including other websites that we operate or the other services that we provide. We also work closely with third parties, including sub-contractors in technical, customer support and payment services as well as advertising networks. 

**How will we use the information about you?**

We use the information we hold about you in the following ways:

  * To administer your Account with us (including notifying you of any potential matches, tips, announcements and updates, should you consent to this). 

  * To help us improve the structure, layout and usability of the Website. 

  * To allow you to participate in any interactive features of the Website. 

  * To help personalize your repeat visits to the Website. 

  * To provide you with information, products or Services that you request from us or which we feel may interest you, where you have consented to be contacted for such purposes. 

  * To answer any questions you may raise or respond to any comments you may send to us. 

  * To notify you about changes to our Services or the functionality of the Website. 

  * To carry out market analysis and research. 

  * To ensure that you are complying with the Terms and to comply with our statutory and regulatory obligations. 

**Disclosure of your information**

As we continue to develop our business, we might sell or buy assets. In a sale transaction, the information we have collected about you will generally be one of the transferred business assets. We may share information about you with: 

  * Other companies in the same corporate group as us. 

  * A buyer or prospective buyer of our business. 

  * Our professional advisers, such as our lawyers, where it is necessary for them to advise us. 

  * Other persons if we are under a duty to disclose or share your information in order to comply with any legal obligation. 

  * Third parties that we engage to help us in certain areas, such as processing payments for Services you order from us. 

We may also provide information about you to other Members and/or Subscribers of the Website as reasonably required in order to provide the Services that you order from us. 

By joining any site within JDI Dating Ltd you agree that we may use your contact information for the purpose of sending or advertising to you, information or promotional material relating to the JDI Dating Ltd network of sites or third party sites. 

You can set your browser not to accept cookies. However, in a few cases, some of the features on our Website may not function as a result. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies when you log on to the Website. 

We advise that all Members and/or Subscribers should take the following precautions when meeting or corresponding with anyone on any dating or social networking website: 

  * Anyone capable of identity theft can also falsify a dating profile; 

  * There is really no substitute for acting with caution when interacting with any stranger or Member and/or Subscriber who wants to meet you; 

  * You should never share your personal details: last name, email address, home address, phone number, place of work, or any other identifying information in your dating profile or initial email messages. We do our best to police the site for potential fraud and scam artists. We advise you to stop communicating with anyone that pressures you for personal or financial information; and 

  * If you decide to meet face-to-face with another Member and/or Subscriber, you should always tell a close friend or family member where you are going and when you are expected to return. Never agree to be picked up at your home. Always be in control of the situation, provide your own transportation to and from your meeting and meet in a public place with many people around. 

Although we do our best to monitor findmelove.com and our affiliates’ content, we cannot guarantee that all material used has consent prior to publication. If you feel that any content should be removed from our site, please do not hesitate to contact us. 

**Where we store your personal data**

The personal data that we collect from you may be transferred to, and stored at, a location outside the European Economic Area (“EEA”). It may also be processed by staff located outside the EEA who work for us or for one of our suppliers (for example, staff who are involved in providing Services that you order from us, processing your payment details or providing support services for the Website). By submitting your personal data to us through the Website, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing. We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy. 

Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password or personal code which enables you to access certain parts of the Website, you are responsible for keeping the password or personal code confidential. We ask you not to share a password or personal code with anyone. 

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to the Website; any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we will use procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorized access. 

**E-Mail Removal**

If you wish to opt-out of receiving all e-mail correspondence from us, please submit your email here. 

**Other Websites**

The Website may, from time to time, contain links to and from the websites of our partner networks, advertisers and affiliates. If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that these websites have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies. Please check these policies before you submit any personal data to these websites. 

**Access to information and correction**

The Data Protection Act 1998 gives you the right to request a copy of the information that we hold about you. If you would like a copy of some or all of your personal information, please contact us at support@date-support.com. Please note that any request is subject to a fee of £10 to meet our costs in providing you with details of the information that we hold about you. We reserve the right to refuse to provide you with a copy of your personal data based on exemptions set out in the Data Protection Act 1998, but if we do refuse we will give reasons for our refusal and allow you to challenge our decision. 

We want to make sure that your personal information is accurate and up to date. You can ask us to correct or remove information you think is inaccurate at any time by contacting us. 

Please note that we do not verify user’s identity when a photo is submitted which means we cannot guarantee all photos are of the person named in the profile. We accept no responsibility for the source of the photo and will remove any photos that are proved to not be of the named user. 

**Cookie Policy: Information about our use of Cookies**

Our Website uses cookies to distinguish you from other Members and/or Subscribers of our Website. This helps us to provide you with a good experience when you browse our Website and also allows us to improve our Website. By continuing to browse the Website, you are agreeing to our use of cookies. 

A cookie is a small file of letters and numbers that we store on your browser or the hard drive of your computer if you agree. Cookies contain information that is transferred to your computer's hard drive. 

We use the following cookies: 

  * _Strictly necessary cookies_ – These are cookies that are required for the operation of our Website. They include, for example, cookies that enable you to log into both general and secure areas of our Website, purchase products or services and to make use of e-billing services. 

  * _Analytical/performance cookies_ – They allow us to recognise and count the number of visitors and to see how visitors move around our website when they are using it. This helps us to improve the way our website works, for example, by aiding users in finding what they are looking for. 

  * _Functionality cookies_ – These are used to recognise you when you return to our website. This enables us to personalise our content for you, greet you by name and remember your preferences. 

  * _Targeting cookies_ – These cookies record your visit to our website, the pages you have visited and the links you have followed. We will use this information to make our website and the advertising displayed on it more relevant to your interests. We may also share this information with third parties for this purpose. 

Please note that third parties (including, for example, advertising networks and providers of external services like web traffic analysis services) may also use cookies. These cookies are likely to be analytical/performance cookies or targeting cookies. 

You can block cookies by activating the setting on your browser that allows you to refuse the setting of all or some cookies. However, if you use your browser settings to block all cookies (including essential cookies) you may not be able to access all or parts of our site. 

Except for cookies essential to the operations of the site, all cookies will expire after the browser closes. These are known as session cookies. 

**Changes to our privacy policy**

We keep our Privacy Policy under regular review and will post any changes to it on this page. We encourage you to regularly review our Privacy Policy to make sure you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances, if any, we may share it with other parties. 

JDI Dating Ltd

Legal Department 

Station House  
North Street  
Havant  
Hampshire  
United Kingdom  
PO91QU

E-mail: legal@date-support.com
